multidmedia.com 2005-03-19

# {mdm} © PRIVACY POLICY

MDM has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

MDM does not sell, lend nor distribute any member information to any third party. Information may be shared with partners that provide co-branded services but this information is limited to that required to implement such services, and will only occur with the member's consent to participate in such services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our Trial Downloads registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their postal/zip code). We use customer contact information (email address) from the registration form to send the user information about improvements, new features, or important changes in MDM's services. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time. 

The MDM site contains links to other sites. MDM is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or the content of such Web sites. When visiting such sites, we urge you to be an informed surfer and use caution when providing any personal data. We may use an outside companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies for optimization purposes, and MDM does not have access to this information.

**PUBLIC SERVICES**

The MDM Support Forum is also bound by this Privacy Policy. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the Support Forums becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**SECURITY**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include secure servers, encrypted passwords, and other security measures to guarantee the privacy of our members. We do not store credit card information on any MDM servers.

**MAILING LISTS**

By downloading a Trial Product at MDM, you agree to subscribe to our Members Update and Special Offers mailing lists. These lists may contain third-party sponsorships. You may unsubscribe to one or both lists at any time. Other lists subscriptions are completely optional and may contain third-party endorsements. You have the following options for removing your information from our database to not receive future communications. You can unsubscribe from any mailing lists by following the instructions contained at the bottom of the emails.

Contacting the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact support@multidmedia.com
